ninjaoutreach.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy | NinjaOutreach

**When you register**

Upon signing up for NinjaOutreach services, we collect information such as full name, email address, and payment details. We may also ask you for details of the company you work for and the telephone number, which is optional to provide.

Note that we will always indicate where any personal information is mandatory or optional.

We use Stripe, a payment processor that helps us collect and store payment details which we are using to bill any amounts that are due from you. This payment processor may collect your address, location, email address, credit card or debit card number, its expiry date and its verification code. NinjaOutreach does not store any payment information.

From the time you become a NinjaOutreach user and/or contact our Customer Support, we automatically collect the following data: IP Address, device type, browser type, operating system.

 _Additional data that we automatically collect:_

  * How many times you have logged into NinjaOutreach
  * Email addresses you used for outreach campaigns
  * Lists you have created and exported
  * How many times you have run a search using NinjaOutreach and what have you searched for

When you import Google Search Results using our Chrome Extension or when you import your own list, we collect and may store information you upload into NinjaOutreach.

We also automatically track certain information about your behavior on our website such as pages you visited, from which page you came from and to which page are you going to.

 **Google user data**

NinjaOutreach is able to integrate with the user’s Gmail account to let users send emails via Gmail API. The service integrates into Gmail and needs to connect with your Google account. The only information we store is the email address of the Gmail account you have connected to our service, the access token, and identifiers for drafts and messages sent through the campaign. We use this information only to provide you with the following services:

  * Email sending through the NinjaOutreach platform on your behalf;
  * Tracking of replies to messages sent through the NinjaOutreach platform;

We require the permission to read your emails in order to be able to fetch any replies from your campaigns.

We require the permission to send emails on your behalf in order to be able to launch campaigns with your account. We never send an email from your Gmail account unless you start a campaign manually from the application or if you use the built-in quick-reply feature in our application’s inbox.

We do not access your Sent emails through your Gmail account. Only the emails you send through NinjaOutreach will be visible in our application’s inbox.

We can add a tracking pixel to the body of emails sent through our service to track email opens and edit links in your emails to track link clicks. We use data acquired through these tracking methods to maintain email campaign operability and provide campaign reports.

You can revoke NinjaOutreach access to your Gmail account on the settings page of your NinjaOutreach account or [here](https://myaccount.google.com/permissions?utm_source=google-account&utm_medium=web). If you decide to do so, we will lose access to your Gmail account and will no longer be able to provide you campaign sending services through Gmail API.

We delete all data collected from your Gmail account upon request.

We do not share or pass data to any third parties under any circumstances. We can only give access to data to authorized authorities upon lawfully authorized requests or in cases of emergency.

The data collected from your Gmail account is not normally accessed by anyone in our team, unless you specifically request support from our Support Agents and allow us to access the data.

 **Children**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the legal age (according to your jurisdiction). If you are under the legal age (according to your jurisdiction), please do not attempt to register for our services or install the NinjaOutreach Chrome extension without verification of parental consent.

If we learn that we have collected personal information from anyone under the legal age (according to the user’s jurisdiction), we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that anyone under the legal age (according to the user’s jurisdiction) has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [support@ninjaoutreach.com](mailto:support@ninjaoutreach.com).

We use this information to process your registration, provide our service, provide statements of account and communicate with you on any matter relating to your account, troubleshoot problems, resolve technical issues, bill any amounts due from you, resolve billing disputes and the provision of our service in general. NinjaOutreach’s Chrome browser extension lets you use some of our services directly through your browser. We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us further develop and improve our service. These statistics will not include any information which can be used to identify you. We may also wish to provide you with information about special offers related to our service or any other service or products which we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, you can always opt-out by clicking the Unsubscribe link in our emails or by contacting [support@ninjaoutreach.com](mailto:support@ninjaoutreach.com).
